Would you like beer?
Or whiskey?
I also got soju
No thanks
Just fill it in
What's this?
It's 100 questions
and answers
Let's fill it in
and memorize it
Weren't you the one
who hated doing this?
You're working so hard
I might as well do it
properly
All the answers
can be searched online
You've never
looked up my name?
Yes, I have
28 years old, a former
member of Alphadog
I just need
more details
You can ask me
anything you want
Wouldn't this be
easier than that?
Weren't you lost
on the way here?
I was gonna go
pick you up, but…
My friend lives here
so I know the way
Friend?
An actor friend?
We used to act together
since childhood
Now he's working
in producing team
You guys must've been
quite close then
Right
We're close
Have you ever heard…
the news
about a child actor
who was missing
at a shooting set
and found later?
Is anybody there?
Anybody?
It's already been
over about ten years
The boy was rescued
from the warehouse